Inventory of the Green Party of California records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Susan King file, 1990-2011
  - "Common Ground,", undated (Box-folder 39:12)
  - Amiee Anderson notes, 2006 (Box-folder 39:13)
- Green Party bumper stickers, 1992-2008 (Box-folder 40:1-3)
- Political stickers, 1990s-2000s (Box-folder 40:4)
- Political flyers, 1990s-2000s (Box-folder 40:5)
- Manifestos and political flyers, 1990s-2000s (Box-folder 40:6)
- Campaign buttons, 1990s-2000s (Box 41)
- Audiovisual material, 1988-2004
  - 3 CD-Rs, 2 DVDs, 2 zip disks, 1 5 inch floppy disk, 33 3.5 inch floppy disks, undated (Box 42)
  - 32 audio cassettes, 1 phonograph record, undated (Box 43)
  - 9 VHS videocassettes, 1988-1993 (Box 44)
  - 15 VHS videocassettes, 1994-2000 (Box 45)
  - 15 VHS videocassettes, 2000-2004 (Box 46)
- Campaign signs and Global Green posters (3 oversize folders), 1990s-2000s (Map case)
- Campaign Posters (Box 47)